theplayerslobby.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy - The Players’ Lobby

Thank you for visiting CLICKON, a site within the network of sites of CLICKON Media. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by CLICKON Media, and to set out the basis on which any personal data we collect about you, or that you provide, will be processed.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 the data controller is CLICKON Media Ltd of 24 Greville Street, London, EC1N 8SS

## The Information We Collect

Through CLICKON, you can engage in various activities such as entering contests or sweepstakes, playing games, taking quizzes, voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion, subscribing to one of our services. Your personally identifiable information may be required to engage in these activities as well as to receive products and services that you may have requested. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include but are not limited to: name, address, gender, e-mail address and telephone number.

We may also collect information that you provide when filling in forms on our site (including when registering to use our site, posting material or requesting services) about your personal or professional interests and use of or opinions about various products, programs and services. For instance, we may ask you to identify your job or industry to qualify you for certain product prizes or holidays.

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages or use our applications, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, your IP address, your device identifiers, your Internet or wireless service provider, and location-based information and the resources that you access.

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a better experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. Our site uses the following cookies for the following purposes:-

Cookie Type| Cookie Name| Purpose  
---|---|---  
WordPress| wp-settings-  
wp-settings-time-  
wordpress_test_cookie| These cookies are required by WordPress and hold no personally identifiable information.  
Buddypress| bp-activity-oldestpage| These cookies are required by Buddypress.  
Website| PHPSESSID| Identifies your current web session to our server. It is set upon your arrival to our site and deleted when you leave. It holds no personally identifiable information.  
Piwik| _pk_id  
_pk_ses| These cookies are required by Piwik.  
Segment| ajs_anonymous_id  
ajs_group_id  
ajs_user_id| These cookies are required by Segment.  
Google Analytics| _ga  
_gid| These cookies are required by Google Analytics.  
  
## How We Use The Information

CLICKON Media may use information you provide about yourself to fulfil requests for products, services, show through our videos, to respond to inquiries about offerings and to offer other content that may be of interest.

We may combine information we receive with outside records and share such information with third parties to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If you  **do not  **want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

When you request a service through CLICKON, we will forward the information you give us to the publisher or provider for fulfilment. They may contact you with special offers of possible interest. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or sweepstakes, or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to contact you about your account.

If you choose to submit content (e.g. uploading videos), we may publish your name, screen name and other information you have provided to us. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites, and to enable us to customize your Internet experience. We also may use this information to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

[All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted [using SSL technology].] Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Please note that if CLICKON Media or any of its subsidiaries or lines of business is merged, acquired, divested, financed, sold, disposed of or dissolved, including through merger of, consolidation, sale or divestiture of assets, the relevant customer database, including personally identifiable information we may possess about you, may, in whole or in part, be sold, disposed of, transferred, divested or otherwise disclosed as part of that transaction or proceeding.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us following the links to the ‘Contact us’ page on the website.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

The Data protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to CLICKON Media Ltd of 24 Greville Street, London, EC1N 8SS.
